Welcome to Larry King Now.
Our special guest is Gary Vaynerchuk.
The self-proclaimed hustler
is a digital media mogul,
author, web show host,
and venture capitalist,
among many other things.
As the CEO and
co-founder of VaynerMedia,
Gary hosts the hugely popular
YouTube show, Ask Gary Vee,
and has penned three
New York Times bestselling books.
Gary has been named to
Fortune Magazine's 40 Under 40
list of the most influential
business leaders and holds
the number one ranking on
Forbes Top 40 Social Selling
Market Masters.
His newest book, Ask Gary Vee,
is available now.
How did this all start?
Wine? What happened with you?
What happened with me is
I had the great benefit of being an immigrant.
I was born in Belarus in the former Soviet Union.
My mother was from Belarus.
I didn't know that.
Minsk, I think.
Yeah, I was born 40 minutes from Minsk.