I think it's important to
highlight why it's not just
about a couple hundred tech
bros in Silicon Valley not
being able to make payroll,
but there's important
downstream consequences.
For example,
there are payment processing companies
in Silicon Valley that use
Silicon Valley Bank to store
their capital and to move
money around.
There are payroll companies
that do payroll for many businesses,
not just tech businesses,
but many businesses in different parts of the economy
that store their cash at Silicon Valley Bank
and process money through Silicon Valley Bank.
Today it was announced that
Rippling, one of those companies,
could not hit their payroll cycle today
because they had money tied up at
Silicon Valley Bank.
Fortunately, they announced that
they also have money at JPMorgan
and other places, so they will
be able to kind of get the
payroll processed early next week
and get everyone back on track.
But this is hundreds and potentially
thousands of companies that use
their payroll software to process and
pay their employees.
You can start to see
how there can be
very significant trickling effects.
And more importantly,
like we saw in 08,
perhaps to a different degree,
but still a significant concern
is the contagion of panic,
where people say,
if there isn't reliability
in the things that I thought
were reliable before,
I start to have real questions
in the soundness of the system overall.
And that's why it's so important,
as Zach said,
to step in,
shore up the problem this weekend.
I don't think it's about
bidding 50 cents or 60 cents
on the dollar.
Every depositor needs to get
paid 100% of their money,
and that cash needs to be
made available to them by
early next week.
And if that money is not available to them
within the first 48 or 72 hours of the end of this weekend,
then we're going to have a real crisis on our hands,
because then you will see a lot of people trying to move money
away from any institution that stores their money in some sort of security
that's not 100% liquid like cash.
That's going to
cause a massive run.
And so what has to happen,
the only way this can happen is if
someone takes over Silicon Valley Bank
this weekend, and that the federal
government, unfortunately, as much as
I hate to say it, because I absolutely
hate the federal government having a
role in this stuff, has to say we will
guarantee 100% of those deposits to
the company that takes over the bank
that takes over this portfolio, and says,
let the portfolio of assets run its
lifetime, see what you get paid,
whatever the delta is, we'll make it up to you.
But we need to make sure
that there's cash here today,
for all of these depositors
to get paid tomorrow.
You had something
you want to say?